# RAKHI **JAIN**

156, Adarsh Colony Daudpur Alwar · 7737189582

Email:- 1996rakhijain@gmail.com · LinkedIn Profile :- https://www.linkedin.com/in/rakhi-jain-48aa77141/

Web Developer specializing in front end development. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML5, PHP, JavaScript, CSS, MySQL, Wordpress.. Strong background in project management and customer relations.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **NOVEMBER 2020 - PRESENT**

#### LARAVEL DEVELOPER, EMIZEN TECH PVT LTD

- Developing PHP based server-side API using Laravel Framework.
- Collaborate with other team members to develop, maintain and produce client projects.
- Developing REST API.
- Good understanding of MVC model and Web design

#### **MARCH 2020 – OCTOBER 2020**

#### PHP DEVELOPER, AVENIR TECHNOSYS LLP

- Responsible for Front-end and Back-end development coding.
- Developing PHP based server-side API using codeigniter.
- Good understanding of MVC model and Web design
- Knowledgeable of Integrating Payment Gateway.

#### **MARCH 2019 - FEBRUARY 2020**

#### PHP DEVELOPER, PROTOVO SOLUTIONS LLP

- Created and Components Web Applications using PHP Programming.
- Created Language site layout and user interface using HTML and CSS practices
- Worked on the custom cms build in codeigniter and used it for many projects based on the requirement.

#### **EDUCATION**

2014-2018

BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY, IET COLLEGE

RTU UNIVERSITY

## **SKILLS**

- Codeigniter
- Laravel
- HTML, CSS, Ajax
- CMS Framework:- Wordpress
- Rest Api
- Node Js
- Git

### **ASSURANCE**

I hereby declare that all the information above is true to my knowledge and concern.